so the revolution starts today because
I'm ready I'm smart enough
I am ready enough which means I am in no
way ready and in no way have it all
figured out and that is why it is
perfect because this single mom who
lives in poverty who's had brain tumors
and brain damage and lives with a DD and
autism has figured out how we create a
better world together but the piece I
wasn't going to share or wasn't sharing
full on was the piece of how I got there
and the piece of how I live my
day-to-day life which is listening to my
own inner voice and moving myself
forward through each individual guidance
and when I listen am at amazing magic
happens for me and this project and when
I don't listen horrible stuff happens
just me so I'm gonna listen because I'm
here to create a better world for
everyone a world of abundance and peace
for every single human being on this
planet and I know how we get there and I
have needed to grow and become more and
more and more in order to accept that in
and of myself and like I could see it
but oh my god yeah why not if you can
see it I don't care I don't care if none
of you can see it I am gonna show up and
be me on repeat and explain what that
means because I need other people to do
the same I need other people to show up
as them to be themselves to be their
authentic human selves they're like
they're their shadow all of it together
and in doing so that by itself is gonna
save the planet but we have an actual
plan an actual plan to do it which is to
create the technology company that we
all own together that creates the
infrastructure to be able to have
knowledge and connection like we have
never before seen on this planet
knowledge that no one human being can
act can create in their own mind it has
to be something we do together and if
one person did it we wouldn't trust it
we have to do it together and we're
going to do it together
and we're gonna do it by me showing up
and being me and I get that that does
not make sense yet I get that I've not
figured out how to explain Matt and that
is perfect like that is what you all get
to participate in is watching that
process happen watching the process of
me continually showing up day after day
after day as I have zero subscribers
I've 19 subscribers actually and with
out video quality without Mike without
those things that normally typically we
have to have all of that we do not
need to have those things what we need
to have is ourselves and what I
currently have is me and my current
technology which is this computer
currently because my kids on the iPad
other days over better quality because
I'll be on the iPad and today this is
what we get and some days I'll speak for
my heart and it will come out
beautifully and amazing and other days
I'm gonna go off on a multiple multiple
two engines and bring it back
and I'm only that's all I have to do and
it's taken three years to keep digging
to the point where I'm ready to be like
I'm showing up I'm showing up live on
YouTube as it will let me because I
don't think the algorithm works anymore
it doesn't let you actually go live what
you have under a certain number of
subscribers so whatever is working now
I'm gonna keep fudge in the system until
it works I don't need to go live I just
need people to subscribe and people to
comment and if nobody ever does that I'm
gonna have an amazing time feed myself
and these will be my video diaries to
see and watch and something else will
come a bit because my mind can logically
plan how all of it happens and
ironically to make it happen I had to
let go of all of that I have to let go
of my need to know absolutely everything
and I'm now ready because time and time
again I have followed the guy
the inner my inner guidance the little
voice it's like do this thing do you got
thing and I know me I'm definitely gonna
go kicking and screaming and I know that
it's going to take a lot and I'm gonna
show up and share that because although
I also know that when I'm in the
vulnerable stage and when it's more or
down and when I'm tired and when my mind
can't think of the words even more so
than it normally does I don't want to
show up and be on camera and I don't
want to be vulnerable in that state but
I'm going to try and I'm going to keep
moving this forward as I have been the
reason why this is day one is I'm
finally like okay right there is no to
be there to get to and I've gotten that
before in the past but not on this level
not on this level of like with the
project I have I'm like yes I get at
videos on great Wix website this is how
it is but with me my inner workings how
I'm figuring out how to create a better
world is by being myself a hundred
percent stop masking stop pretending
stop doing any and I'm that person all
of the time now I'm that person all at
the time I show up with my true emotions
and my true feelings and my true
thoughts and I'm ready to do that even
in a world that it's not kind when you
do that because I'm strong enough I'm
strong enough to get through this thing
with my sister and still survive and I'm
strong enough to get through brain
surgery twice and radiation once I am
strong enough to keep on showing up
bringing the vulnerability and moving
this forward and so right now my
universe has to reverse the inner
guidance of God I don't know I don't
even know where it comes from it's just
magic I like feel like I have to create
an entire religion it's basically this
isn't a religion but it works thank
figure you know who you are and
listening to that inner guidance and
then your magic happens because
mine's not gonna work for you you have
to listen to the interior and they're
all gonna be different because your
interior self does not listen to society
and it's it only is like right
so I need to quit my job well that seems
there
it's like if that might be what you need
to do that's not what I need to do but
that might be what you would need to do
and I've seen other people that is
absolutely needed to do I don't yet know
where it's best it doesn't mean I'm
necessarily gonna be on YouTube every
day doing it but I'm gonna try because I
have the feeling that YouTube and
Facebook are the two that are the most
powerful my issue is like I don't want
to show up and be and like waste that
before being ready for it and I thought
that meant technologically that I have
to be ready for I've learn in a video or
someone else has to come on board first
you know it's how to edit video but
that's not what happens
it meant I had to be ready I have to be
ready to show up and do exactly what it
is on the deeper and deeper level and so
right now my guidance is to do the
curable app which I'm going to do and
showcase because I'm ready to not I'm
ready to let go of this pain in my body
okay people that and I'm ready to UM to
go for a walk in nature every day and
argue out loud with my guides and look
like a crazy person because it's amazing
and I highly suggest it whatever you're
saying it's not everyone needs to be
walking around actually like a crazy
person but you'll probably get there
when you get there you'll understand how
amazing it is you don't care that you
look like a crazy person you don't care
what anyone else thinks of you because
this is what is no one can pay you not
to be yourself once you tap into being
yourself there is no relationship that's
worth not being yourself there's no job
that's worth it there's no anything
that's worth it and so that is what and
I'm realizing those people over here
chatting hello hello although it says
zero now it's funny it was like people
and then hi and then they it left and
then the things came on sometimes these
things are just not here but I'm going
to be showing up daily I'm gonna try it
for daily and when I don't I'll just
come on when I'm able and then
oh not and it's just hopefully the idea
I love that any of my ideas actually go
forward in the way that I want they go
forward in the perfect way not the way
that I have plans and my thought is that
enough people will show up and be okay
with being their ascent
self by me showcasing it that we can
create this world together then I'm also
gonna be talking about because it's all
it's all together do you what is with
people you and people on YouTube and
we'll deal with that we will block
people who are ridiculous human beings
but everyone else is invited everyone
else who is not a troll is invited to
the revolution come as you are show up
as you are and we are going to create a
better world together starting with
ourselves being authentic and amazing
and then we will create that space for
everybody else and I just wanted to come
on and share that I don't want this to
go too long so hoping that people will
eventually watch it and if it's over ten
minutes they definitely will so take
care and I will see you all tomorrow